Nobody is enough just for being nice.
And I know somebody's like,
well, no, what we mean when we say nice girls
is that we not like city girls.
We're not in here in the streets.
Like we not just out here doing whatever, whatever.
And that's what we mean by the men.
Like they not out here doing whatever, whatever either.
I hear that.
And my thing to that is that I just feel like the bar is low
when we're just like, I'm not a criminal.
Like, I feel like the bar is low
when it's like, I'm not a cheater.
Like that's what makes you a nice guy or a nice girl.
How about you are about something,
you are in purpose and you have intention.
And on top of that, you're not a .
Let's be that.